export const DESKTOP_WIDTH = 1280;

export const TABLET_WIDTH = 768;

export const MOBILE_WIDTH = 540;

export const initialQuestions = [
  { 
    question: 'The eccentric Jim Moran once brought a bull to a china shop. Another time he brought several tons of dried grass to the city and for almost four days... What did he do?', 
    answer: 'searched for a needle',
    hint: 'So Moran tested various sayings - for example, about a bull in a china shop and about the difficulty of finding a needle in a haystack.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'Protodeacon Karpenko told that there were no Xs on the ark, because faith is X. Tal Barahi temple is located in an unusual place, but tourists are helped to get there. Therefore, sometimes in the temple among the bright flowers you can see Xs. Name X.', 
    answer: 'Life vest',
    hint: 'The temple is located on a small island, where tourists get by boats, wearing life jackets for safety reasons.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'According to Isaac Asimov, the outcome of one battle between the Arabs and the Persians was decided by the unexpectedly started IT. Another IT began on February 16, 1991. Name it in three words.', 
    answer: ' Desert Storm',
    hint: 'The wind blew on the Persians, sand flu in their eyes, and they were forced to flee.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'According to Chuck Palahniuk they are designed to make us feel better about the random, useless facts that are all we have left of our education.', 
    answer: 'Game Shows',
    hint: 'Quizzes'
  },
  { 
    question: 'On February 15, 2013, a meteorite flew over Chelyabinsk. A few minutes later, numerous videos of an unusual phenomenon filmed by eyewitnesses appeared on the Internet. Videos have become popular all over the world. But in Germany access to most of them was banned. Why?', 
    answer: 'Background music',
    hint: 'Copyright is strictly enforced in this country.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'In the trailer for Wolfenstein: The New Order, you can see Germans crossing the street, a Nazi flag is in an unusual place, and a soldier on a European city square... Doing what?', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'A few years ago, the basketball player Marcus Morris had a son. After that, Morris added to his playing kitâ€¦ what did he add on his kit?', 
    answer: 'Sr.',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'One famous American writer was terribly upset by the way that his book in a Japanese translation bearing the title The Angry Raisins. What was the original name of the book?', 
    answer: 'The Grapes of Wrath',
    hint: 'The John Steinbeck novel'
  },
  { 
    question: '8', 
    answer: ' searched for a needle',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: '9', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
  { 
    question: '10', 
    answer: ' searched for a needle',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: '11', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
];